(Episode 14)
- Eun Seo.
- Jun Seo.
I can't come for three days.
Will you be okay?
No, I'll come the day after tomorrow.
I'm leaving. See you in two days.
No, I don't think so.
I'll come tomorrow. I'm coming tomorrow.
Take care of things at work,
and drive safely.
When you say that...
I might wish for something again.
I would dream you said "drive safely"
every morning,
and gave me a kiss,
then I'll be fully confident
to do anything.
I'm going to visit your family this time,
and...
No.
You can't say anything before
Jun Seo leaves. Never.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I won't say anything.
I won't tell Jun Seo.
I'm shrewd, aren't I?
Jun Seo has only a few days
before he leaves.
Don't you want to meet him
for the last time?
Okay.
I should get going.
Thanks.
Yes.
Okay.
Sure.
I'm sorry, Tae Seok.
I'll be out for just one day.
Because it would be the last time,
and it is to say goodbye,
I just need a day.
Yes, okay.
It wouldn't take long since
it's just a venous blood sampling.
Please book a hotel near the hospital.
Her mother and brother are coming first.
Yes.
Yes, I'll call you later.
There is no better option
other than a bone marrow transplant.
We should ask her family members first
to get tested.
Can't I do it? Is mine not going to work?
We wouldn't worry
if anyone could be a donor.
Even though the patient doesn't want it,
please contact her family
as soon as possible.
Are you leaving today?
Yes.
As for everything left here,
you can throw them away.
Why is that? Are you not coming back?
No. I will leave it as it is.
Come back with Eun Seo next time.
Will you?
What are you doing here?
Didn't you go to work?
You don't need to do that.
It can splatter on your clothes.
It did already.
What?
Did I get something on my face?
You've gotten soft.
You used to scold me...
when I wasn't helping you at your store.
Why are you here?
Your daughter, Eun Seo, asked me...
to look after you.
That's nonsense.
She should mind her own business.
She's not treating you very well, either.
Is that why you're here?
I just stopped by.
Stay at the store.
I'm getting vegetable oil.
I'll go. I can drive to get it.
No, I'll go. I need to buy
some other ingredients as well.
It's fine. I'll go and get some.
Poor things,
both Eun Seo and you.
Hi, hello.
You're here.
It's a humble house.
Are you coming from Seoul?
How is Eun Seo doing?
She's not giving me her phone number.
Is she doing well?
How is her new job?
Ms. Soon Im.
Is something wrong?
Did something happen to Eun Seo?
Look at me.
Please tell me.
Tell me.
What's going on?
What happened to Eun Seo?
Eun Seo...
is sick.
She is very sick.
Is she...
It's cancer, Ms. Soon Im.
She has cancer.
She needs a bone marrow transplant,
and the doctor insisted that
her family members get tested first.
That's why I came here.
What a cruel man.
He had given me so much
of a hard time before he died.
And as if that wasn't enough,
he even gave her cancer.
What an evil man.
Tae Seok.
Is it true?
Sin Ae.
Does Eun Seo have cancer?
Does she really have cancer?
Tae Seok, tell me.
I think I deserve to know.
Tell me.
If Eun Seo has cancer,
Mom, Dad, and Jun Seo,
what about them?
Don't tell them.
Don't say anything to anyone.
Don't tell Jun Seo.
- Tae Seok.
- That's what Eun Seo wants.
So, you should forget what you heard.
If you tell Jun Seo about this,
I won't ever forgive you.
Wait, please stop.
Eun Seo.
Why can I...
Why can I not get away from you?
No.
Eun Seo.
Why did you let him travel when there are
only a few days left before leaving?
I let him because we have a few days.
So that he can do anything he wants
without regrets before we leave.
I wish you could have gotten married
before you leave.
Eat it, Sin Ae.
Mom.
Why are you...
Hello.
What are you doing?
Are you out of your mind?
Why did you come here?
What's going on?
This is all I have.
What is this?
It's not a lot of money,
but this is all I have. Please use this.
I know it costs so much money.
Her dad died from that disease, too.
Please help, for old time's sake...
Mom.
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
Please save her.
My Eun Seo...
My Eun Seo is...
She is dying from the same disease.
Mom.
Please let her get the surgery at least.
I don't have anyone to ask for help.
You used to be her parents,
so please save her.
You save her, please.
Save her.
What do you mean by that?
What do you mean by "save her?"
Whom should we save?
Save her.
- Mom.
- Ms. Kyung Ha.
Mom.
What should I do?
It's up to you.
I'm thinking only about
what I should do as well.
If Jun Seo gets to know about this...
If he gets to know...
Don't tell Jun Seo.
Isn't that what you want, too?
I haven't told him.
Why haven't I?
Eun Seo doesn't want him to know it.
That's what she wants.
My only excuse for not telling him
is that it's what Eun Seo wants.
Let's think only about
what we want for ourselves.
I will think of myself.
What should I do?
Aren't you cold?
No.
Are you leaving soon?
Yes, I have only a few days.
I wanted to come here before leaving.
I wanted to tell you something here.
"Goodbye." "See you again."
I was going to say those lines.
If you say that here, I wouldn't hear you.
You wouldn't?
You're mean.
I thought you would always hear me
if I said something.
So, when we were apart,
I've always talked to you.
Didn't you hear that?
I didn't hear it.
I heard it. Of course, I heard it.
You said you missed me.
Yes.
Longing to see you, missing you,
and missing you so much.
Because I always miss you
even when I'm looking at you.
Where are you now?
Are you in Seoul?
Can we not talk about that?
Acting as if we're in a dream,
can't we just look at each other
like this?
Let's stay like this just for a day.
Just for one day.
Only one day in my life.
Not only one day,
but I wish I could stay like this forever.
Or I want to die like this.
No.
You can't.
I'll die first. Don't you remember that?
Jun Seo.
We'll love each other forever,
only in our hearts.
Only in our hearts.
We'll love each other in our hearts...
and not hurt Yu Mi and Tae Seok,
who love us.
Who cares if it is only pretense?
Let's just lie.
And be happy, all of us.
Even if we run away...
Even if we run away, we can't be together.
So, I will have only your heart.
You already took mine.
You already...
have mine, too.
What's wrong? Are you tired?
No, I just fell.
You're clumsy. Let's go.
Eun Seo.
Jun Seo, can you give me a piggyback ride?
Give me a piggyback ride.
Okay.
Hop on.
Why are you so quiet?
Because I might be heavy.
Jun Seo, I love you.
I love you, Jun Seo.
You're strange.
Jun Seo, do you know that?
You've told other people you love me,
and yet you've never told me that
looking into my eyes.
What did you say?
Eun Seo, I love you.
You've never told me that.
Eun Seo, I...
No.
Not now. Tell me later.
Later.
Later when?
The day when we meet again?
Yes.
Yes, when we meet again,
so until then, you must practice
saying it nicely.
Then, tell me when we'll meet.
Until then...
I'll be waiting for you,
looking forward to that.
I promise to wait for you.
I'll be waiting for you.
To hear you tell me you love me,
I'm going to wait for that.
We love each other forever,
only in our hearts.
Only in our hearts.
We'll love each other in our hearts...
and not hurt Yu Mi and Tae Seok,
who love us.
Who cares if it is a pretense?
Let's just lie.
And be happy, all of us.
Are you going to the hospital?
Yes.
I'll see how her condition is.
Also, I'm worried about Eun Seo.
You shouldn't worry about it too much.
I'll call you when I see the doctor.
I'll go with you.
No.
I'll check first, and call you later.
And,
don't tell Jun Seo for now.
Don't tell him.
Dad.
Do as I say.
If he knows Eun Seo is sick,
he will lose his mind.
We don't know for now,
but we would have to move on.
Let's tell him when Eun Seo gets better.
Do you understand?
Get in a hurry to leave for the U.S.
Jun Seo being here is not helping Eun Seo.
Honey.
How could you say that?
You also shouldn't say anything
to Jun Seo for now.
Honey.
- Don't say another word.
- Honey.
You know this already.
What would happen
if Jun Seo gets to know about it?
I don't know.
All I know is that Eun Seo is sick.
She is sick and dying.
So how could you say that?
Don't. Stop it, and let's go.
No.
Don't touch me.
I'll go by myself.
You don't deserve to meet Eun Seo.
Ms. Kyung Ha.
Mom.
Professor Yoon.
Don't say anything to Jun Seo.
If we lose both of them,
she and I won't even survive.
Don't ever tell him.
She has been unfortunate,
and she gets into even worse situations.
She'll be fine.
She has to.
Our Eun Seo will be all right.
It'll be fine.
Are you waiting for Tae Seok?
Yes.
Do you want to see who came?
Mom.
Are you in much pain?
My Eun Seo.
You got so thin.
You should eat well.
Yes.
I eat well, Mom.
Does it hurt?
No, it doesn't hurt at all.
We don't have water. I'll get water.
No, I'll go.
It is so good to have two moms, right?
When I call out "Mom,"
you both answer with "yes."
Mom?
Yes.
Jun Seo doesn't know about this, does he?
Eun Seo.
He doesn't, does he?
No.
That's good.
I feel so bad about making you upset, Mom.
No.
Eun Seo, no.
If I...
don't make it...
Don't.
Eun Seo, don't. Don't say that.
I can't live if you're gone.
I'll die, too.
Because you would be lonely all alone,
I'll follow you.
Mom.
Don't say that.
I don't like that.
Okay, Eun Seo.
I'm sorry. I won't say it like that.
Eun Seo.
Is this garlic?
Come here.
Jun Seo.
- You're here, Yu Mi.
- Yu Mi.
I'm sorry.
We ran out of gas in our kitchen.
Jun Seo hasn't come back.
Jun Seo.
I thought you wouldn't come back.
Why wouldn't I?
I'm sorry.
Are you worried?
Probably...
Mine wouldn't match...
since she's not my biological daughter.
Because we have different blood types,
I lost her.
But I feel like they might match,
so can I get tested?
Since her brother's test doesn't match,
I hope yours does.
Yes.
I hope so.
If she were my biological daughter,
it might have been easier to get surgery.
If she were my biological daughter...
No, not for me.
If she weren't my daughter,
this cancer...
she wouldn't have had this
at such a young age.
If she weren't my daughter...
If she weren't my biological daughter...
Yu Mi.
What can I do?
What should I do, Eun Seo?
I'm fine.
Yu Mi, I'll get better.
I'll survive.
So, don't cry.
And...
- Eun Seo.
- Don't tell him.
Don't ever say it to Jun Seo.
When he comes back from the U.S.,
I'll tell him while smiling.
"Jun Seo, I was very sick before."
I'll tell him like this.
Eun Seo.
It's not for you.
It's not for Jun Seo, either.
It's for me.
I...
don't want him to see me like this.
Do you understand?
It's for me.
I understand.
Okay.
Eun Seo, please live.
You must live, and when we come back
from the U.S.,
we will meet again.
Please don't die like this.
It's also for me,
for me...
I'll live.
I'm getting surgery soon.
I'll get better.
Eun Seo.
I'm sorry.
Yu Mi.
Please make Jun Seo happy.
That's the only thing I wish for now.
Make him happy, please.
Yu Mi.
Where have you been
this early in the morning?
I just took a walk to get fresh air.
I've been thinking about
how I could make you happy.
I'll make you happy.
I'm leaving for the U.S. next semester.
Please feel free to contact me
if you ever come to the U.S.
I'll treat you.
Anyway, all of you have done great work
for this semester. Good job.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Let's think about good things.
Good reasons.
If I get five good reasons
for you to live,
I'll do whatever I want.
Your mom and dad.
That's one.
And...
the beach.
The beach?
That's two.
Making a confession.
How did you know that?
I have my way of knowing. That's three.
And...
spicy rice cakes.
How did you know that?
And the last one is...
All right, why not?
Yoon Jun Seo.
Okay, now I will do whatever I want.
Survive, Eun Seo.
Don't give up.
Please live.
Can I say something, too?
One more good reason for me to live.
That is Tae Seok.
Thank you.
I have enough.
What you said is enough.
That's enough for me.
Eun Seo.
No.
Eun Seo, no.
No, Eun Seo.
No.
Eun Seo, no.
It's so weird.
It was a very strange day.
Yu Mi.
Jun Seo.
Jun Seo, what should we do?
What should we do, Jun Seo?
Eun Seo is...
Eun Seo?
Eun Seo is dying.
She is dying.
She's in a coma.
What do you mean?
Why is Eun Seo in a coma?
Eun Seo is sick.
I lied to you.
Jun Seo, what should we do?
What should we do?
What if she dies?
(Intensive Care Unit)
Where is Eun Seo?
- Jun Seo.
Get off of me.
- You're not allowed.
- You can't come in.
I need to go in.
Get off of me.
I need to see her.
I have something I didn't say.
I have something I haven't told her.
You told me to tell you
when we meet again.
I haven't told you I love you.
Eun Seo.
I love you, Eun Seo.